DNS maintenance scheduled for Wednesday, 25th

Buy/Sell HNS

About HNS

Support

[Marketplace
-----------](https://www.namebase.io/domains)[Auctions
--------](https://www.namebase.io/auctions)

Buy/Sell HNS
------------

About HNS
---------

Support
-------

[Log In
------](https://www.namebase.io/login)[Sign Up
-------](https://www.namebase.io/register)

Last revised on: February 17, 2021

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how Namebase Inc., Namebase US, Inc. and its related companies (collectively, “Company” “Namebase”, “us”, “our”, and “we”) collect, use and share personal information of consumer users of https://testnet.namebase.io, https://namebase.io, or any associated websites, APIs, or mobile applications (collectively the “Site”). This Policy also applies to any of our other websites that post this Policy. This Policy does not apply to websites that post different statements.

The bank, Evolve Bank & Trust, Member FDIC, that powers certain banking services and products offered through us has updated its privacy policy. We encourage you to read the updated privacy policy, which can be found here https://synapsefi.com/evolve-privacy.

By signing up to use an account through the Site, you agree that you have read, understood, and accept all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Any capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in the Namebase Terms of Use (“Terms of Use”).

WHAT WE COLLECT

We get information about you in a range of ways

* Information You Give Us. We collect your name, postal address, email address, date of birth, username and password, as well as other information you directly give us on our Site. In addition, we may collect certain personal information (e.g., social security number or other proof of identity such as driver’s license, passport or government-issued ID”) in order to verify and authenticate your identity as required by applicable law. To use certain Namebase Services, you may also be required to provide certain financial information.

* Information We Get From Others. We may get information about you from other sources, including from publicly available data on a blockchain network such as information collected from using blockchain explorers. We may add this to information we get from this Site. We also receive information about you from third party services we partner with to verify and authenticate your identity as required by applicable law.

* Information Automatically Collected. We automatically log device information when you access the Site and use the services. For example, when visiting our Site, we log your computer operating system type, browser type, browser language, the website you visited before browsing to our Site, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times and information about your use of and actions on our Site.

* Cookies. We may log information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. This type of information is collected to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use your personal information as follows:

* We use your personal information to operate, maintain, and improve the Site, products, and Namebase Services.

* We use your personal information to create your Namebase Account.

* We use your personal information to process and deliver auction entries and rewards on the Handshake Blockchain.

* We use your personal information to respond to provide customer service.

* We use your personal information to send information including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages.

* We use your personal information to communicate about promotions, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by us and our selected partners.

* We use your personal information to link or combine user information with other personal information as part of our process to verify and authenticate your identity as required by applicable law.

* We use your personal information to protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity or money laundering.

* We use your personal information to enable you to access and use certain Namebase Services in connection with the purchase or sale of Handshake Coins.

* We use your personal information to conduct security investigations and risk assessments.

SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share personal information as follows:

* We may share personal information with your express consent.

* We may share personal information when we do a business deal, or negotiate a business deal, involving the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These deals can include any merger, financing, acquisition, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.

* We may share personal information for legal, protection, compliance and safety purposes.

* We may share information to comply with applicable laws.

    * We may share information to respond to law enforcement, officials, regulatory agencies and other lawful requests, subpoenas and legal processes.

    * We may share information to protect the rights and property of Namebase Inc., our agents, customers, and others. This includes enforcing our agreements, policies, and terms of use.

    * We may share information in an emergency. This includes protecting the safety of our employees and agents, our customers, or any person.

    * We may share your information with financial institutions with which we partner to provide you certain Namebase Services.

    * We may share your information with corporate affiliates.

    * We may share your information with certain service providers to help provide the Namebase Services, including certain third-party identity verification partners.

INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES

Our marketing emails tell you how to “opt-out.” If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include emails about your Namebase Account and our business dealings with you. You may send requests about personal information to our Contact Information below. You can request to change contact choices, opt-out of our sharing with others, and update your personal information.

You can typically remove and reject cookies from our Site with your browser settings. Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings. If you remove or reject our cookies, it could affect how our Site works for you.

INFORMATION SECURITY

We take your privacy very seriously and work hard to protect Namebase and you from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of information we collect and store. We encrypt the Site using SSL encryption technology and all traffic on the Site is forced to use SSL.

We review all information practices on a regular basis, and we restrict access to information on a need-to- know basis for all employees and other Namebase service providers who are subject to confidentiality obligations and are subject to termination or disciplinary action, including legal action, should such employees or service providers breach these obligations. While two factor authentication is not presently required to access the Site and use Namebase Services, we reserve the right to require use of two factor authentication in the future.

PROTECTING CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY

The Namebase Services are only intended for use by those who have reached age 18 and older. By using the Namebase Services you are affirming that you are at least 18 years old. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided information to us, please notify us at alert@namebase.io. If we inadvertently collect information of children under 13, we will delete that information immediately upon notice. We are not liable for any damages that may result from the user’s misrepresentation of age.

CONTACT INFORMATION

We welcome your comments or questions about this privacy policy. You may also contact us at our address: Namebase US, Inc. ATTN: CEO Address: 340 S Lemon Ave. #4341 Walnut, Ca 91789 United States Telephone: (857) 540-5647 Email: hello@namebase.io

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

This privacy policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes, we may notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us (if any), and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Site. You are responsible for providing us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. Continued use of our Site and the Namebase Services following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

Learn

Product

Company

Developers

Support

©2024 Namebase, Inc | Banking services are provided by Synapse's bank partners, Members FDIC
